prekindle.com 2015-06-07

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY Date of last revision - May 19th, 2015

First, you should know that we believe protecting your privacy is our duty and one of the best ways to gain your respect. We want your respect. We like to be on the right side of things.

When you purchase tickets through Prekindle, you will supply us with the information required to perform the credit card transaction, deliver your receipt(s), and identifying information that will be used during the will-call process at the event. We will keep this information and it may include your:

  * Name
  * Billing Address
  * Phone Number
  * Email Address
  * What You Bought

We do not keep your full credit card number on file, we only keep the last four digits in case there is a discrepancy or refund claim at a future time.

We keep this information in our records so we will be able to support you if any issues arise after your purchase. If you need a receipt re-sent, we can do that quickly and easily. If you are entitled to a refund, we know how much to give you. We only use your information to fulfill our business relationship with you. 

The venue and organizer of the event you attend will have your name and purchase details on their will call list to facilitate entry. The organizer may allow you to opt out of being contacted for purposes other than communication about this event. This option will be clear during the purchase process, and if chosen your contact information will not be shared.

Absolutely not. Our business is helping the local scene run smoothly and selling tickets to events. We get paid by doing that successfully. We only use your information to fulfill our business relationship and will not sell this information with any third parties. 

We use non-identifying information about where people are purchasing what to help performers decide where to go. This means your purchase will contribute to our knowledge of the market. ie: there is one more person in Town A that is seeking performances by Band B. However, there will not be a name with the number.

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our practices and services. When we post changes to this Privacy Policy, we will update the "last revised" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes in the way we collect, use, and/or share your personal information, we will notify you by prominently posting notice of the changes on our website. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to remain updated as to any changes in our privacy or other policies.

Please contact Prekindle Customer Support 

if you have other questions regarding your privacy
